Trajkovska Maja

Contact

Phone:

+389 75 357228

Email:

majatrajkovska85@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/trajkovska.maja

Languages

Macedonian English Russian Serbian

Summary

Expert associate in administration for pension and disability insurance and special category of insurance at the same field. Administrative and functional expert with ability to understand and implement policies, procedures and processes that relate to HR strategic and office plan.

Skill Highlights

- HR management
- Problem solving
- Teamwork

- Comunication
- Organisation
- Employee rallations

Experience

- Data officer in insurance 2006-2007
- -A income officer for pension retirement 2008-2014
- Expert associate for pension and disability insurance for special category of insurance
- *All work positions require communication with people,so I have developed experience of HR functions, administrator or other HR position

Company – Pension and disability insurance fund of R.Macedonia

Education

- -Bachelor degree : University St.Kiril and Metodij,Faculty of Philology 2004-2012
- -Education centre Brainster: Full stack HR Academy -2022